Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2011 - Series VI: Other Administrative Files, 1992-2000
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries B: Memos
    - Memos [May 19, 1998 - Dec 17, 1998] (Box 56 a, Folder 3)
    - Memos [Jan 12, 1999 - Oct 12, 1999] (Box 56 a, Folder 4)
    - Memos [Oct 19, 1999 - Mar 14, 2000], 1999-2000 (Box 56 a, Folder 5)
    - Memos [Mar 21, 2000 - Dec 12, 2000] (Box 56 a, Folder 6)
- Accretion 2011 - Series VIII: Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated
  - [Barbara Kruger] [1/3], undated (Box 56 b, Folder 7)
  - [Barbara Kruger] [2/3], undated (Box 56 b, Folder 8)
  - [Barbara Kruger] [3/3], undated (Box 56 b, Folder 9)
  - [Barbara Kruger Reviews Clippings], undated (Box 56 b, Folder 10)
  - [Federico Uribe Clippings Book], undated (Box 56 b, Folder 11)
- Accretion 2011 - Oversize Series VIII: Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated
  - [Barbara Kruger], undated (Box 54, Folder 16)